dnforum.com 2004-12-04

# 

DNForum.com is committed to respecting your privacy rights when visiting DNForum.com discussion forum. To protect your personal information, DNForum.com has adopted the guidelines outlined below. 

**Information Collected**  
While visiting DNForum.com, we may ask you to register and/or provide information that personally identifies you for purposes of interacting with the site. Such personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, street address and e-mail address. On any page that collects personal information, we will specifically describe what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service, as well as respond to your inquiry or comment. 

**What are Cookies?**   
A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program. The site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the site. We cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. Additionally, we cannot learn your e-mail address or any other information about you through the use of a cookie. The only way we would learn such information is if you specifically and voluntarily submit that information to us, for example, through a registration system, by entering a sweepstakes or promotion, etc. 

**Why does the site use cookies?**   
DNForum.com uses cookies to track usage of the site and further personalize your experience when you are visiting the site. By tracking usage, we can best determine what features of the site best serve the users. 

**What benefits do I receive from cookies?** Overall, the use of cookies helps to give you a more personalized experience at the site. The information is used to keep our site fresh and relevant to you the user. Cookies also allow you to avoid retyping your e-mail address and password each time you access the site. 

**May I decline to accept a cookie?**  
You may decline to accept cookies sent by the site by selecting an option on your browser to reject cookies. However, some portions of the site may require registration in order to access those areas. In such cases, we ask that you register and provide us with basic information on our registration page, or sign in if previously registered. Cookies enable our server to know that you are a registered user; and will eliminate the need for you to log in each time you access our site. In addition, our registration system may require that you accept the cookies from the site in order to access that portion of the site. Other sites linked to the site may also send cookies; however we do not control such activities. 

**What happens with the information collected in a cookie?**  
The information stored in a cookie is used to identify you to our server, to allow us to personalize your experience on the site, and to serve content and communications that may be of interest to you. 

**IP Addresses** DNForum.com does log IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes and to determine site usage. 

**Use of Personal Information**  
We believe in protecting your privacy, and will not share personal information with third parties outside of DNForum.com. We believe that we can enhance your experience on our site with the information you share with us. We use personal information about you to improve our advertising and marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to personalize the sites content, layout, and services. We may also use your personal information, such as your e-mail address or mailing address, to contact you regarding products and/or services that may be of interest to you, to respond to an inquiry from you regarding the information that we have collected or respond to your comments and suggestions.   
**Under no circumstances DNForum.com will not sell you personal information or user database to outside companies.**   
We have today, and will in the future have, arrangements with third party service providers, such as credit card processors. When you sign up for a service we offer on the site, we may be required to share Personal Information with that service provider in order to provide the service. These third party providers are not permitted to retain or use personal information for any purpose unrelated to providing the service.   
We reserve the right to disclose personal information when needed to comply with the law or a legal process, cooperate with investigations of purported unlawful activities or to identify persons violating the law. 

**Childrens Privacy**  
DNForum.com cares about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, in accordance with the Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical. 

**Reviewing, Changing and Deleting Your Personal Information**  
You may at any time choose to change or your profile or disable your account. You should know that as a result of deregistration, certain areas of the forum may no longer be accessible to you. 

**Security**  
DNForum.com maintains industry standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personal information that you provide to DNForum.com 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [support@dnforum.com](mailto:support@dnforum.com)
